Finding Aid for Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies (University of Michigan) Records, 1892-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean's Topical Files, 1892-2010
  - 1968-1991, bulk 1975-1991
    - Honors Mentorship Program, 1988-1989 (Box 119)
    - International Academic Affairs
      - Committee on UM Post Soviet Activities, 1993 (Box 119)
      - Correspondence, 1992-1993; 3 folders (Box 119)
      - Director Search, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 140)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2023 ]
      - International Activities-Joint Advisory Committee on, 1992-1993 (Box 119)
      - International Institute, 1992-1993 (Box 119)
      - International Linkages (Box 120)
        - General, 1992-1993 (Box 120)
        - China, 1992-1994 (Box 120)
        - Japan, 1992-1993 (Box 120)
        - Korea, 1992-1993 (Box 120)
        - Mexico, 1992-1993 (Box 120)
        - Russia and Eastern Europe, 1992-1993 (Box 120)
        - South Africa, 1992-1993 (Box 120)
      - Personnel, 1992-1993 (Box 120)
      - "Preparing for an International and Global World" Survey, 1993 (Box 120)
    - International Partnership Program, 1989-1990 (Box 120)
    - International Programs, 1988-1989 (Box 120)
    - International Studies
      - General, 1988-1991; 3 folders (Box 120)
      - South African Initiative, 1991 (Box 120)
      - Swain Proposal, 1986 (Box 120)
      - Taiwan Proposal, 1989 (Box 120)
    - Jerome Lectures, 1986-1990 (Box 120)
    - K, 1986-1990 (Box 120)
    - Kelsey Museum, 1984-1991 (Box 120)
    - L, 1989-1991 (Box 120)
    - Latin American Studies, 1988-1989 (Box 120)
    - Lecture Hall, Rackham, 1983-1990 (Box 120)
    - Library
      - Electronic Publishing, 1980-1988 (Box 120)
      - University, 1988-1991 (Box 120)
    - Livingston Awards, 1987-1990 (Box 120)
    - M, 1986-1989 (Box 120)
    - Michigan Annual Giving Fund, 1976-1981 (Box 120)
    - Michigan Council of Graduate Deans, 1985-1991 (Box 120)
    - Michigan Journalism Fellows Program, 1986-1991; 2 folders (Box 120)
    - Michigan Quarterly Review, 1971-1989 (Box 120)
    - Michigan Society of Fellows (Box 121)
      - Ford Foundation Proposal, 1970-1981; 2 folders (Box 121)
      - Reports and Recommendations to Ford, 1976-1977 (Box 121)
    - Middle English Dictionary, 1973-1990 (Box 121)
    - Midwestern Association of Graduate Schools, 1987-1990 (Box 121)
    - Minority Affairs
      - Rackham, 1986-1991; 2 folders (Box 121)
      - University, 1988-1991 (Box 121)
    - Minority Faculty Development Fund, 1989 (Box 121)
    - Museums
      - General, 1985-1986 (Box 121)
      - Art Museum, 1983-1991; 2 folders (Box 121)
    - N, 1987-1991 (Box 121)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1989-1990 (Box 121)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH), 1987-1991
      - Cheney Report, 1988 (Box 121)
      - Research Panel, 1988 (Box 121)
    - O, 1986-1990 (Box 121)
    - P-Q, 1990 (Box 121)
    - Pew Scholars Program, 1986-1990 (Box 121)
    - Postdoctoral Students, 1990 (Box 121)
    - Program Development, 1975 (Box 121)
    - Program Evaluation/Review, 1973-1991; 2 folders (Box 121)
    - Psychological Clinic, 1987-1991 (Box 121)
    - Publication Subventions, 1982-1990 (Box 121)
    - R, 1980-1988 (Box 121)
    - Racism Issues, 1987-1988 (Box 121)
    - RaJAH (Rackham Journal of the Arts and Humanities), 1971-1986 (Box 121)
    - Reading and Learning Skills Center
      - General, 1986-1990 (Box 121)
      - Review Report, 1984 (Box 121)
    - Residency, 1972-1991 (Box 121)
    - Society of Fellows (Box 122)
      - Budget, 1984-1990 (Box 122)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1991 (Box 122)
      - Executive Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 122)
      - Junior and Senior Fellows Selection, 1984-1991 (Box 122)
    - Teaching Assistant Awards, 1986-1991 (Box 122)
    - University Press
      - Book Awards, 1976-1991 (Box 122)
      - Correspondence, 1985-1991; 2 folders (Box 122)
      - Executive Committee, 1985-1991; 2 folders (Box 122)
      - Financial Subcommittee, 1988-1990 (Box 122)
      - Financial Statements, 1985-1991 (Box 122)
      - Hamilton Prize (Women and Gender), 1977-1990 (Box 122)
      - "Plan Towards Excellence,", 1985-1986 (Box 122)
    - Visiting Scholars Program, 1977-1985 (Box 122)
  - 1985-1996
    - Health Insurance
      - 1987-1996, 8 folders (Box 154)
    - Papers Given at "New Faces, New Ideas, New Realities: Symposium in Honor of Dean Nancy Cantor,", November 8, 1998 (Box 154)
    - Student Initiated Combined Degree Program (SIDP), 1977-1996 (Box 154)
    - Tax Issues, 1985-1988; 2 folders (Box 154)
  - 1972-1999, 1985-1996
    Dean's Topical Files, 1972-1999 subseries (8 linear feet) continues the series from previous accessions. The files in this subseries span the years from 1972 to 1999, with the bulk of the material from 1989 to 1995. Most date from the deanship of John D'Arms (1985-1995), but small amounts of material from Interim Dean Robert Weisbuch (1995-1996), and Deans Nancy Cantor (1996-1997) and Earl Lewis (1997-1999) are also included. A researcher interested in the organizational structure of Rackham during this time period should consult the files within this series that specifically relate to Rackham as an organization, including the Dean's Briefing Book and Rackham External Administrative Review from 1996, and the Rackham Briefing Book from 1999.
    Of particular note are the agendas, minutes, and supporting materials from the Rackham Deans Meetings, which lend insight into the major issues and priorities of Rackham during this time period. Also prominent is administrative correspondence between the Dean and the academic units, centers, and programs under his/her budgetary control or with which the dean had significant involvement. These units include the Institute for the Humanities, the Museum of Art, the University of Michigan Press, and the Michigan Journalism Fellows program.
    - A-Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 174)
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2022 ]
    - Academic Affairs, Office of the Vice Provost, 1992-1994; 2 folders (Box 174)
    - Academic Affairs, Office of the Vice President and Provost
      - General, 1990-1992 (Box 174)
      - Annual Report, 1993-1995 (Box 174)
    - Academic Integrity, 1992-1994 (Box 192)
      [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2069 ]
    - Admissions-Rackham
      - General Correspondence, 1991-1996; 2 folders (Box 192)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2068 ]
      - Pilot Project, 1991-1994 (Box 174)
      - Statistics, 1991-1992 (Box 174)
      - Student, 1991-1993; 2 folders (Box 192)
    - Admissions-University, 1991 (Box 174)
    - Area Centers Study Committee, 1991-1992; 3 folders (Box 174)
    - Association of American Universities/Association of Graduate Schools Project for Research on Doctoral Education
      - General, 1991-1995 (Box 174)
      - Executive Committee, 1991 (Box 174)
      - Steering Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 174)
      - Relocation Efforts, 1992-1993 (Box 174)
    - Association of Graduate Schools
      - General Correspondence, 1991-1996 (Box 174)
      - Annual Meetings Agenda, 1991-1994 (Box 174)
    - B-Miscellaneous, 1992-1995 (Box 174)
    - Bentley Library, 1991-1993 (Box 174)
    - Budget-Rackham
      - 1993-1994 (Box 174)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 174)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 174)
    - C-Miscellaneous, 1992-1994; 2 folders (Box 192)
    - Child and Family, University Center for
      - General, 1988-1994 (Box 174)
      - Jerry Miller, Director, 1994 (Box 192)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2024 ]
      - Oscar Barbarin, Director, 1991-1994 (Box 192)
      - Director Search, 1992 (Box 192)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2022 ]
      - Neil Kalter, Director, 1987-1992 (Box 192)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for, 1991-1993 (Box 175)
    - Clements Library
      - General, 1991-1993; 2 folders (Box 175)
      - Budget, 1992-1994 (Box 175)
      - Committee of Management, 1993-1995 (Box 175)
      - John Dann, Director, 1991-1994 (Box 192)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC), 1996 (Box 175)
    - Council of Graduate Schools (CGS), 1994-1996 (Box 175)
    - D-Miscellaneous, 1993-4 (Box 175)
    - Deans Meetings
      - 1994-1995, 3 folders (Box 175)
      - 1993-1994, 4 folders (Box 175)
      - 1992-1993, 4 folders (Box 175)
      - 1991-1992, 4 folders (Box 175)
    - Dissertation Policies, 1990-1994; 2 folders (Box 192)
    - Dissertation/Thesis Grant, 1994 (Box 176)
    - Diversity
      - Rackham, 1992-1994 (Box 176)
      - University, 1989-1994 (Box 176)
    - Doctor of Arts Proposal, 1972 (Box 176)
    - E-Miscellaneous, 1992-1994 (Box 176)
    - Education of Women, Center for, 1992-1995 (Box 176)
    - Enrollment Planning, 1991-1995 (Box 176)
    - Evolution and Human Behavior, Program on, 1990-1993 (Box 176)
    - F-Miscellaneous, 1991-1995 (Box 176)
    - Faculty Awards-D'Arms Awards, 1996 (Box 176)
    - Faculty Grants and Fellowships Policies, 1991-1995 (Box 176)
    - Fellowships
      - Minority
        - Barbour Scholars, 1991-1994 (Box 176)
        - Patricia Roberts Harris Fellowship, 1993 (Box 176)
        - Research Careers for Minority Students, NSF Traineeships, 1992 (Box 176)
        - South African Mid-Career Fellowship, 1992 (Box 176)
      - Specific
        - Dean's Fellowships, 1991-1996; 2 folders (Box 176)
        - Fulbright Fellowship, 1991-1993 (Box 176)
        - German Exchange Fellowship, 1991-1994 (Box 176)
        - Guggenheim Fellowships, 1992 (Box 176)
        - Jacob Javits Fellowship, 1991-1993 (Box 176)
        - National Science Foundation Fellowships, 1991-1996
          - Supplements to NSF Fellowships-GradCare vs. Stipend, 1993 (Box 176)
        - Newcombe Fellowship, 1993-1996 (Box 176)
        - Non-Traditional Fellowships, 1991-1996 (Box 176)
        - Power Fellowship, 1991 (Box 176)
        - Predoctoral Fellowships, 1991-1995 (Box 176)
        - Rackham Merit Fellowships, 1992-1994 (Box 176)
        - Rackham One-Term Dissertation Fellowships, 1991-1994 (Box 176)
        - Regents Fellowships, 1991-1994 (Box 176)
        - Spencer Fellowship, 1992-1996 (Box 176)
    - Financial Aid, 1993 (Box 176)
    - Foundations
      - Delmas Foundation, 1994 (Box 176)
      - Ford Foundation
        - General, 1993 (Box 176)
        - Survey, 1995 (Box 176)
      - General Electric Foundation, 1992-1995 (Box 176)
      - Howard Foundation, 1988-1991 (Box 176)
      - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 176)
      - Kress Foundation, 1991 (Box 176)
      - McArthur Foundation, 1993 (Box 176)
      - Packard Foundation, 1988 (Box 176)
      - Searle Foundation, 1991 (Box 176)
      - Spencer Foundation, 1993 (Box 176)
      - Whitaker Foundation, 1992 (Box 176)
      - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation, 1988-1993 (Box 176)
    - Foundation Fund Raising Committee, 1990-1994 (Box 176)
    - G-Miscellaneous, 1988-1995 (Box 177)
    - Gerontology, Institute of, 1992 (Box 177)
    - Governors, Rackham Board of, 1987-1995; 2 folders (Box 177)
    - Graduate Employees Organization
      - General, 1993-1994 (Box 177)
      - Advisory Group, 1989-1991 (Box 177)
    - Graduate Student Forum, 1991-1994 (Box 177)
    - Graduate Student Survey, 1995 (Box 177)
    - H-Miscellaneous, 1990-1995 (Box 177)
    - Hatcher, Harlan, 1992-1993 (Box 177)
    - Health Insurance-Graduate Students, 1991-1994 (Box 177)
    - Historica Critica, 1985 (Box 177)
    - Honors Convocation, 1990-1992 (Box 177)
    - Human Adjustment, Institute for
      - General, 1980-1996; 4 folders (Box 177)
      - Robert Hatcher, Director, 1993-1994 (Box 192)
    - Human Growth and Development, Center for
      - General, 1992-1993 (Box 177)
      - John Hagen, Director, 1985 (Box 192)
    - Humanities Institute
      - Conferences, 1987-1991 (Box 177)
      - Correspondence
        - 1993-1994 (Box 177)
        - 1987-1991 (Box 177)
      - Director Search, 1994; 2 folders (Box 192)
      - Executive Committee, 1991-1995; 2 folders (Box 177)
      - External Review, 1992 (Box 177)
      - NEH/Challenge Grant, 1988 (Box 177)
    - I and J-Miscellaneous, 1991-1994 (Box 177)
    - International Institute
      - General, 1993-1996 (Box 177)
      - Director, 1994 (Box 192)
      - Executive Committee, 1993-1995 (Box 178)
      - Governing Board, 1994 (Box 178)
    - International Programs, 1988-1994 (Box 178)
    - International Studies, 1991-1993 (Box 178)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for (Box 192)
    - K-Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 178)
    - Kelsey Museum, 1985-1992 (Box 178)
    - L-Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 178)
    - Language and Culture Group, 1987-1993 (Box 178)
    - Latin American Studies, 1989-1993 (Box 178)
    - M-Miscellaneous, 1989-1994 (Box 178)
    - Mellon Humanities Chapter, 1995 (Box 178)
    - Michigan Journalism Fellows
      - General, 1987-1996; 3 folders (Box 178)
      - Budget, 1987-1995 (Box 178)
      - Director, 1987-1996; 2 folders (Box 192)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2026 ]
      - Review, 1996 (Box 178)
    - Museum of Art
      - General, 1991-1995 (Box 178)
      - Budget, 1990-1993 (Box 178)
      - Director, 1991-1992 (Box 192)
      - Graham Smith, Interim Director, 1988-89 (Box 192)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2019 ]
      - Evan Maurer, Director, 1980-88 (Box 192)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2018 ]
      - Personnel, 1983-1993 (Box 192)
    - N-Miscellaneous, 1991-1994 (Box 178)
    - Near Eastern and North African Studies, Center for, 1991-1994 (Box 178)
    - O-Miscellaneous, 1991-1994 (Box 178)
    - Overview of Rackham, 1985-1995 (Box 178)
    - P-Miscellaneous, 1992-1994 (Box 178)
    - Policy File, 1975-1995 (Box 178)
    - Population Studies Center, 1991-1994 (Box 178)
    - Sarah Goddard Power Award, 1993 (Box 178)
    - Presidential Initiatives Fund, 1987-1994 (Box 178)
    - President's Office Correspondence, 1987-1994 (Box 179)
    - Provost's Administrative Group (PAG), 1990-1993 (Box 179)
    - Psychological Clinic
      - General, 1987-1995 (Box 179)
      - Director, 1987-1993 (Box 192)
    - Public Policy Studies, Institute of, 1989-1994 (Box 179)
    - R-Miscellaneous, 1991-1994 (Box 179)
    - Rackham Student Government, 1979-1994; 2 folders (Box 179)
    - Reading and Learning Skills Center, 1986-1996 (Box 179)
    - Regents, Board of, 1993-1995 (Box 179)
    - Regent Philip Power, 1988-1994 (Box 179)
    - Research, Office of the Vice President for, 1985-1995; 2 folders (Box 179)
    - Teaching, Center for, 1993-1995 (Box 179)
    - S-Miscellaneous, 1991-1995 (Box 179)
    - Senate Assembly, 1990-1992 (Box 179)
    - Social Research, Institute for, 1991-1995 (Box 179)
    - Society of Fellows
      - General, 3 folders
        - 1986-1996 (Box 192)
        - 1994 (Box 192)
      - History, 1970-85 (Box 179)
    - Stebbins, William, 1991 (Box 179)
    - Strategic Retreat, 1987-89, 3 folders (Box 179)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for, 1992-1994 (Box 179)
    - T-Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 179)
    - Taxation of Graduate Student Tuition Waivers, 1988-89 (Box 180)
    - Teaching and Research Assistants, 1990-1996 (Box 180)
    - Teaching Assistant Training, 1995 (Box 180)
    - Time to Degree and Attrition, 1991-1994; 3 folders (Box 180)
    - Training Grant/Cost Sharing, 1993-1994 (Box 180)
    - U and V-Miscellaneous, 1992-1994 (Box 180)
    - Undergraduate Experience, 1990-1994 (Box 180)
    - University Press
      - Book Awards, 1992-1995 (Box 180)
      - Budget, 1987-1991; 2 folders (Box 180)
      - Editorial Board, 1996 (Box 180)
    - University Microfilms, 1993 (Box 180)
    - W-Miscellaneous, 1992-1996 (Box 180)
    - Wallenberg Fellowship, 1990-1997 (Box 180)
    - Wallenberg Lectureship, 1991-1997; 2 folders (Box 180)
    - X, Y and Z-Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 180)
    - Robert Weisbuch, Interim Dean
      - Speaking Engagements, 1990-1996 (Box 180)
      - The Talking Cure, 1995 (Box 180)
    - Nancy Cantor, Dean
      - Children's Centers Unit Review (Box 180)
      - Dean's Briefing Book, 1996; 2 folders (Box 180)
      - Deans Group Working Notes/Matrix, 1997; 2 folders (Box 180)
      - Deans Meetings
        - 1997, 2 folders (Box 181)
        - 1996, 2 folders (Box 181)
      - Dearborn Campus Visit, 1997 (Box 181)
      - Distinguished Dissertation Awards Symposium, 1997 (Box 181)
      - Evenings at Rackham, 1996 (Box 181)
      - Graduate Career Fair for Biomedical and Health Sciences, 1997 (Box 181)
      - Graduate Student Symposium in Medicinal Chemistry, 1997 (Box 181)
      - Interdisciplinary Committee on Organizational Studies (ICOS), 1996 (Box 181)
      - Outstanding Graduate Student Instructor (GSI) Awards Luncheon, 1997 (Box 181)
      - Political Science Lunch, 1997 (Box 181)
      - Rackham Development, 1995-1996 (Box 181)
      - Rackham Executive Board, November 13, 1996 (Box 181)
      - Rackham External Administrative Review, 1996; 2 folders (Box 181)
      - Rackham Merit Fellowship Reception, 1997 (Box 181)
      - Debbie Stabenow, 1996 (Box 181)
    - Earl Lewis, Dean
      - Eggertsen Dissertation Prize
        - Correspondence, 1981-1995; 2 folders (Box 181)
        - History, 1979-1999 (Box 181)
      - A. Leon Higginbotham-Honorary Degree, 1997 (Box 181)
      - Rackham Briefing Book, 1999 (Box 181)
  - Earl Lewis, 1982-2008
    - AAU Public Awareness of Graduate Education (PAGE), 1999-2001 (Box 196)
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2034 ]
    - Admissions Office, 1997-2003; 2 folders (Box 196)
    - Affirmative Action, 1996-2002 (Box 196)
    - Alumni Association, 1999-2004 (Box 197)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1999-2001 (Box 197)
    - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS), 1999-2001 (Box 197)
    - APG Subcommittee Meeting, 2001-2002 (Box 197)
    - Association of American Universities (AAU), 1998-2002 (Box 197)
    - Association of Graduate Schools (AGS), 1997-1999 (Box 197)
    - Autism Center, 1997-2002; 2 folders (Box 197)
    - Barbara Brush, 2004 (Box 197)
    - Black Agenda for the 21st Century, 1998-1999 (Box 197)
    - Board of Governors, 1992-2001 (Box 197)
    - Building Renovation, 2000-2002; 4 folders (Box 197)
    - CARAT/Rackham IT, 2002 (Box 197)
    - Center for Afroamerican and African Studies (CAAS), 1997-2002 (Box 197)
    - Center for Education for Democracy, 2001-2003 (Box 197)
    - Center for Human Growth and Development, 2002 (Box 197)
    - Center for Learning Through Community Service, 1997 (Box 197)
    - Center for Research Learning and Training (CRLT), 1999-2002 (Box 197)
    - Center for Statistical Consultation and Research (CSCAR), 1997 (Box 198)
    - Center for the Education of Women (CEW), 1992-1998 (Box 198)
    - CEW and FCRP Talk, 1997 (Box 198)
    - Clinical Faculty Issues, 1997 (Box 198)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC), 1996-2002 (Box 198)
    - Comparative Studies in Society and History, 1996-2000 (Box 198)
    - Comparative Study of Social Transformations (CSST), 1997 (Box 198)
    - Conference of Southern Graduate Schools, 2004 (Box 198)
    - Conflict/Dissertation Forms, 2001 (Box 198)
    - Correspondence
      - Chancellor Daniel Little at Dearborn, 2001 (Box 198)
      - Dean's Retreat, 1999-2001 (Box 198)
      - Dorcetta Taylor, 2001 (Box 198)
      - Fawwaz Ulaby, 2001 (Box 198)
      - NASULGC Rio Grande Puerto Rico, 2001 (Box 198)
      - National Communication Association, 2001 (Box 198)
      - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 2001 (Box 198)
      - Royster Harper and Bill Zellers, 2001 (Box 198)
      - South African Initiative and International Institute, 1990-1996 (Box 198)
      - University of Washington, 2001 (Box 198)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 198)
    - Correspondence, 1997-2004; 2 folders (Box 198)
    - Council of Graduate Schools Audit, 2003 (Box 198)
    - Council of Graduate Schools Conference Call, 2003 (Box 198)
    - Council of Graduate Schools, 1997-2000 (Box 198)
    - Council of Graduate Schools, 2000-2002; 2 folders (Box 199)
    - Dean Lewis Rackham Files (Box 199)
    - Dean's Group, 1996-1997 (Box 199)
    - Dean's Meetings, 1994 (Box 199)
    - Development Seminar for Deans, 2003 (Box 199)
    - Development, 1997-2003 (Box 199)
    - Dialogues on Diversity, 1998-2001 (Box 199)
    - Dissertation Chair: Policy on Research Scientists, 1993-1994 (Box 199)
    - Dissertation Committee Problems, 2001 (Box 199)
    - Distinguished University Professorship, 1991-2003; 3 folders (Box 199)
    - Diversity Initiatives, 1999 (Box 200)
    - Doctor of Physical Therapy, 2001 (Box 200)
    - Duderstadt/Goldenberg, 2000 (Box 200)
    - DUPs and SPGuide, 2004 (Box 200)
    - Economic Dinner Group, 2003 (Box 200)
    - Engaged Citizens Education for a Diverse Democracy, 2003 (Box 200)
    - English Language Institute, 2002 (Box 200)
    - Executive Board Meeting, 1989-1991; 1996-2000; 2 folders (Box 200)
    - Exit Surveys PhD, 1997 (Box 200)
    - Facilities Office, 1993-2003 (Box 200)
    - Faculty Grievances and Employment, 1998-2004 (Box 244)
      [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2079 ]
    - Fawwaz, Marvin, June, 2003 (Box 200)
    - Fellowship Guidelines/Reports, 1997-1999 (Box 200)
    - Fellowships Barbour Awards, 1997-2002 (Box 200)
    - Fellowships Fannie and John Hertz Foundation, 1998-2000 (Box 200)
    - Financial Aid Presentation 6+1, 2003 (Box 200)
    - First Year Student Survey, 1997-2001 (Box 200)
    - Follow-up Grad Student Leadership Conference (Box 200)
    - Forte Foundation, 2003 (Box 200)
    - Furniture Appraisal for Insurance, 2001 (Box 200)
    - Future of the Research University, 1998-2000 (Box 200)
    - General, 2000 (Box 200)
    - GEO/GSI, 1985-2002 (Box 200)
    - Ginsburg Center, 1998-2004 (Box 200)
    - Graduate Employees Organization (GEO), 1996-1997 (Box 200)
    - Graduate School/OVPR Merger Review, 1982-1984 (Box 200)
    - Graduate Student Forum, 1998-2002 (Box 200)
    - Graduate Student Leadership Conference, 2003 (Box 201)
    - Graduate Student Parents Task Force, 2002 (Box 201)
    - Grant Reviews Provost Office, 1998-2002 (Box 201)
    - GRE Spring Committee Meetings Research Committee, 2003 (Box 201)
    - GRE Summer Board Meeting, 2003 (Box 201)
    - GSI Orientation with CRLT, 2000 (Box 201)
    - GSI Orientation, 2004 (Box 201)
    - GSI Teaching Orientation, 2000 (Box 201)
    - Henry Russell Lecture, 1998-2004 (Box 201)
    - Hewlett Foundation Initial Partnerships Travel, 1980-1987 (Box 201)
    - Higher Education Challenges Michigan League, 2003 (Box 201)
    - Honorary Degree Awards, 1997-2000 (Box 201)
    - Honorary Degrees, 2000-2002 (Box 201)
    - Horace and Mary Rackham Undergraduate Scholars, 1995-1999 (Box 201)
    - Hovey Lecture, 2003 (Box 201)
    - IHA Internship Accreditation, 1997-1999 (Box 201)
    - IHA Review, 2007-2008 (Box 201)
    - Imagining America, 2000 (Box 201)
    - Infrastructure Study, 1996-1997 (Box 201)
    - Institute for Human Adjustment (IHA), 1994-2002; 2 folders (Box 201)
    - Institute for Research on Women and Gender, 1997-2001 (Box 201)
    - Institute for Social Research (ISR), 1996-2001; 2 folders (Box 201)
    - Institute for the Humanities, 1996-2002 (Box 201)
    - Interdisciplinary Committee on Organizational Studies (ICOS), 1994-2003 (Box 201)
    - Interdisciplinary Seminars, 1999-2001 (Box 201)
    - Internal Communications Meeting, 2001 (Box 202)
    - International Center, 2000-2002 (Box 202)
    - International Students, 1999-2002 (Box 202)
    - ITS General, 1999-2001 (Box 202)
    - Jonathan Metzel, 2001 (Box 202)
    - King Chavez Parks Fellowship, 1997-2000 (Box 202)
    - Knight-Wallace Fellows, 1991-2001; 4 folders (Box 202)
    - LGBT Advisory Committee, 1994-1997 (Box 202)
    - Library Computing Environment, 2002 (Box 202)
    - Library Fellowship, 1998-1999 (Box 202)
    - Life Sciences Commission, 1999-2003 (Box 202)
    - Living-Learning Center, 1999 (Box 202)